////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
// This file is created for custom gamemode: Dota 2 Old Beta. //
// 			DO NOT CHANGE ANYTING THERE!	      			  //
////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////

"addon"
{
		//Beta units description (lore)
		  // Skeleton King
		"npc_dota_hero_skeleton_king_hype"												"Blast enemies with hellfire from your hellish blade! Exude a vampiric aura! Strike your enemies critically! Reincarnate instantly, returned to full vigor, in order to punish anyone foolish enough to strike you down!"
		  
		  // Necrolyte
		"npc_dota_hero_necrolyte_hype"													"Unleash a wave of pestilence! Cast an aura that stills your enemy's hearts! Steal a bit of mana from every foe you fell! Rejoice as weakened opponents are mowed down before the Reaper's Scythe!"
		
		  // Wisp
		"npc_dota_hero_wisp_hype"			"Wisp has a talent for making allies more effective. A powerful companion, the wisp's tether speeds allies and stops enemies. Capable of linking to and teleporting across the battlefield with an ally, Wisp can make a dangerous ally even deadlier."

		 // Obsidian Destroyer
		"npc_dota_hero_obsidian_destroyer_hype"			"Stealing from the minds of those he imprisons, Obsidian Destroyer turns raw intelligence into destructive power. Weakening enemies with a barrage of arcane energy, he shatters their sanity with his ultimate blast, often erasing mana from those that survive."		 

		 // Lycanthrope
		"npc_dota_hero_lycan_hype"			"As a man or as a wolf, Lycanthrope devastates enemies with sharp claws and deadly jaws. Summoning stealthy wolves to scout ahead or assault a foe, his wolf transformation grants him the speed and strength to run down his enemies, or escape an ambush."

		 // Doom Bringer
		"npc_dota_hero_doom_bringer_hype"    											"Devour enemy creeps whole! Scorch the battlefield in hellish flame! Gamble with targets' lives. Inflict the devastating curse of doom upon enemy heroes!"

		 // Windrunner
		"npc_dota_hero_windrunner_hype"													"Skewer your opponents with your piercing arrow! Devastate distant foes with your power shot! Move like the wind, overtaking enemies with your blistering attack speed!"

		//Panorama settings
		  // Homepage text
		"beta_homepage"			"Homepage"	
		  
		  // Changelog text
		"beta_changes"			"Changelog"
		
		  // Developers text
		"beta_dev_text"			"Developers"
}
